Mexriniso Jo'rayeva

Junior Front-End Developer

+998 (95) 707 32 16

- @ jurayevamehriniso1@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mehriniso-jurayeva-9a7536282/
- Surkhandarya, Uzbekistan

SUMMARY

Entry-level front-end developer with 2 years of experience in maintaining and building web pages. Seeking for new opportunities and challenges that will expand my skill set. Most proud of 'My E-commerce' - an online service I

developed in my junior year that lets freelancers and students know which clothes shops have various clothes.

EDUCATION

JavaScript Engineering

GPA

Record Mir IT center

2024 - Present

Surkhandarya, Uzbekistan

4.0 / 4.0

Took extra classes in JavaScript, React, Redux, UX and UI

Web Developing

GPA

Tenx IT center

2023 - 2024 Surkhandarya, Uzbekistan

4.0 / 4.0

Learnt HTML,CSS,JavaScript, and their frameworks

EXPERIENCE

Junior Front-End Developer

Record Mir IT

2024 - Present

Surkhandarya,

Drouin is a website that connects skilled and verified instructors with people that want to learn how to drive.

- Completed 100 hours of training on Web Development with React
- Successfully performing maintenance on the front-end of the platform, which is based on React, and Redux
- Communicated with back-end developers for any front-end problematic issues

INDUSTRY SKILLS

HTML **CSS SCSS** Bootstrap React Redux Tailwind JavaScript **GIT** UI UX

STRENGTHS



Eager to learn new skills

As a person who is starting out, I am constantly seeking for new ways to grow and expand my skill



Not afraid of failure

Strong believer in the mantra that we learn from our mistakes.



Time management

I always set aside time to plan my week and distribute the workload by days so that I can simultaneously meet deadlines and maintain my well-being.



Collaborative

Playing in my college's hockey team taught me everything there is to know about being a team player.

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO **PROJECTS**

My E-commerce

🗰 2017 - Present Seattle, WA

https://redux-ecommerce-jvjv.vercel.app/

My E-commerce is an e-commerce website for my first

Developed it in my junior class with 8 of my